<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RenalGuard</string>

    <!-- Score screen -->
    <string name="score">Sepsis Risk Score (Infection Likelihood)</string>
    <string name="patient_score">Patient Score</string>
    <string name="total_score">Total Score</string>
    <string name="scale_label">Scale</string>
    <string name="recommendations">Infection Prevention Strategies</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>

    <!-- Hardcoded numbers (used for warnings cleanup) -->
    <string name="five">5</string>
    <string name="seven">7</string>
    <string name="ten">10</string>
    <string name="fifteen">15</string>
    <string name="eighteen">18</string>
    <string name="nineteen">19</string>
    <string name="twenty_five">25</string>
    <string name="arrow">arrow</string>

    <string name="about_us_text">
        Renal Guard App: IJV Line Risk and Health for Dialysis\n\n
        Overview:\n
        The Renal Guard App is a clinical decision-support tool specifically designed to help healthcare professionals evaluate and manage the risks associated with internal jugular vein (IJV) catheter use in patients undergoing hemodialysis.\n
        IJV lines, while essential for short- or medium-term vascular access, carry inherent risks such as infection, thrombosis, and catheter dysfunction.\n
        This app integrates patient-specific parameters into a comprehensive scoring system (maximum 25 points) to guide evidence-based interventions.\n\n
        Key Features and Functions:\n
        1. Risk Scoring for IJV Catheters\n
        • Calculates a total risk score based on multiple clinical factors including duration of catheter placement, patient comorbidities, history of infections, catheter care practices, and lab parameters.\n
        • Risk levels are categorized as low, moderate, or high.\n\n
        2. Sepsis Risk Assessment\n
        • Uses clinical and laboratory markers to classify sepsis risk into mild, moderate, or severe.\n
        • Offers prompts for immediate clinical actions in high-risk cases.\n\n
        3. Line Management and Infection Prevention\n
        • Provides recommendations on when to replace the IJV catheter.\n
        • Suggests best practices for infection control.\n\n
        4. Antibiotic Decision Support\n
        • Recommends whether empirical or targeted antibiotics should be initiated.\n
        • Integrates local antibiogram data to optimize antibiotic selection.\n\n
        5. Vascular Access Planning\n
        • Advises on transition to an arteriovenous fistula (AVF) in CKD patients.\n\n
        6. Dietary Guidance\n
        • Offers tailored dietary recommendations.\n\n
        7. Appointment Scheduling and Follow-up Tracking
        • Allows patients to book, view, and manage dialysis appointments directly through the app.\n
        • Enables doctors to monitor their daily and upcoming schedules, ensuring better coordination and time management.\n
        • Sends notifications and reminders for upcoming sessions or missed appointments.\n
        • Supports real-time synchronization between doctor and patient dashboards for efficient communication and workflow.\n\n
        Benefits:\n
        • Streamlined Clinical Workflow\n
        • Improved Patient Safety\n
        • Optimized Long-Term Care
    </string>
</resources>
